Guide to the Gregory Breit Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1932-1973; Series I; 14.5 linear feet (29 boxes)
  - Smyth, Henry D., 1944-1948, 1954, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 901, Reel 13U)
  - Snell, Arthur H., 1954 (Box 22, Folder 902, Reel 13U)
  - Snowdon, Stanley C., 1959, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 903, Reel 13U)
  - Snyder, R. H., 1946 (Box 22, Folder 904, Reel 13U)
  - Societa Italiana di Fisica, 1963-1964, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 905, Reel 13U)
  - Society For Freedom in Science, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 906, Reel 13U)
  - Sofustun, A. M., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 907, Reel 13U)
  - Sommerfeld, A., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 908, Reel 13U)
  - Sood, P. C., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 909, Reel 13U)
  - Sources for History of Quantum Physics, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 910, Reel 13U)
  - Southwest Center for Advanced Studies, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 911, Reel 13U)
  - Space Physics Laboratory, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 912, Reel 13U)
  - Spitzer, Lyman, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 913, Reel 13U)
  - Springer-Verlag (Lange & Springer), 1954, 1956-1959, 1962, undated (Box 23, Folder 914, Reel 13U)
  - Sprung, Donald, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 915, Reel 13U)
  - Stafford, G. H., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 916, Reel 13U)
  - Stagat, Robert, undated (Box 23, Folder 917, Reel 13U)
  - Stahl, Carroll Clifford, II, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 918, Reel 13U)
  - Staley, R. C., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 919, Reel 13U)
  - Stanford University, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 920, Reel 13U)
  - Stanford University Press, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 921, Reel 13U)
  - Stapp, Henry P., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 922, Reel 13U)
  - State University College on Long Island, 1958-1960 (Box 23, Folder 923, Reel 13U)
  - State University of New York at Albany, 1968-1969, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 924, Reel 13U)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo, 1966-1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 925-928, Reel 13U)
  - State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1963, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 929, Reel 13U)
  - Staunton, Lawrence P., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 930, Reel 13U)
  - Stechert-Hafner, Inc., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 931, Reel 13U)
  - Stehn, J. R., 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 932, Reel 13U)
  - Steigert, Frederick E., 1953 (Box 23, Folder 933, Reel 13U)
  - Stelson, Paul H., 1954, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 934, Reel 13U)
  - Sterne, Theodore E., 1943, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 935, Reel 13U)
  - Sternheimer, Rudolph M., 1950, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 936, Reel 13U)
  - Stoddard, Carlos F., 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 937, Reel 13U)
  - Sugawara, Masao, 1955, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 938, Reel 13U)
  - Superintendent of Documents, U. S. Goverment Printing Office, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 939, Reel 13U)
  - Swan, Peter, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 940, Reel 13U)
  - Swedish Royal Academy of Science, 1943-1944, 1951-1953, 1956-1957, 1963-1964, 1972-1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 941-942, Reel 13U)
    Nobel Committee for Physics
  - Symposium on Heavy-Ion Scattering, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 943, Reel 13U)
  - Synek, M., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 944, Reel 13U)
  - Szilard, Leo, 1934-1936, 1941, 1960, 1961, undated (Box 23, Folder 945-946, Reel 13U)
  - Taft, Horace, undated (Box 23, Folder 947, Reel 13U)
  - Talmi, Igal, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 948, Reel 13U)
  - Tape, Gerald F., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 949, Reel 13U)
  - Taschek, Richard F., 1941, 1946-1954, 1956-1958, n.d (Box 24, Folder 950-951, Reel 13U)
  - Tata Institute of Fundamental Research, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 952, Reel 13U)
  - Taylor, A. E., 1958, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 953, Reel 13U)
  - Telegdi, Valentine Louis, 1966, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 954, Reel 13U)
  - Teller, Edward, 1939-1940, 1946-1955, 1957-1958, 1960, 1962-1963, 1965, 1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 955-957, Reel 13U)
  - Temmer, George M., 1956, 1962, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 958, Reel 13U)
  - Temple University, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 959, Reel 13U)
  - Textbook Associates, Inc., 1961 (Box 24, Folder 960, Reel 13U)
  - Thaler, Roy M., 1954, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 961, Reel 13U)
  - Thomas, L. H., 1947-1948, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 962, Reel 14U)
  - Thomas, Robert G., 1954-1956 (Box 24, Folder 963, Reel 14U)
  - Thorndike, E. H., 1961, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 964, Reel 14U)
  - Time Life Books, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 965, Reel 14U)
  - Titterton, E. W., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 966, Reel 14U)
  - Tiwari, Prabhakar, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 967, Reel 14U)
  - Tobey, A. R., 1948 (Box 24, Folder 968, Reel 14U)
  - Tobocman, W., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 969, Reel 14U)
  - Tolhoek, H. A., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 970, Reel 14U)
  - Toll, John S., 1956, 1964, 1968-1969, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 971, Reel 14U)
  - Topical Conference on Isobaric Spin in Nuclear Physics, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 972, Reel 14U)
  - Toth, K. S., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 973, Reel 14U)
  - Trippe, Juan T., 1947-1948, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 974, Reel 14U)
  - Truswell, Arthur E., 1956 (Box 24, Folder 975, Reel 14U)
  - Turchinetz, William E., 1969 (Box 24, Folder 976, Reel 14U)
  - Turkevich, Anthony, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 977, Reel 14U)
  - Tuve, Merle A., 1939-1940, 1943, 1946-1954, 1956-1957, 1962-1963, 1968, 1970-1972, undated (Box 24, Folder 978-980, Reel 14U)
  - Überall, Herbert, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 981, Reel 14U)
  - Uhlenbeck, George E., 1971 (Box 24, Folder 982, Reel 14U)
  - Ulam, Stanislaw M., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 983, Reel 14U)
  - Úlehla, Ivan, 1965, undated (Box 24, Folder 984, Reel 14U)
  - Unicard Corporation, undated (Box 24, Folder 985, Reel 14U)
  - Union Carbide, 1950-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 986-989, Reel 14U)
  - United Public Workers of America, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 990, Reel 14U)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1946-1948, 1950-1951, 1953-1954, 1956-1957, 1965, 1968, undated (Box 25, Folder 991, Reel 14U)
    National Bureau of Standards
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 992, Reel 14U)
    Office of Technical Services
  - United States Department of Justice, 1958, 1962, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 993, Reel 14U)
    Federal Bureau of Investigation
  - United States Department of State, 1948, 1951, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 994, Reel 14U)
  - United States Air Force, 1949, 1964, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 995, Reel 14U)
  - United States Air Force, 1954, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 996, Reel 14U)
    Air Research and Development Command
  - United States Army, 1948-1949, 1952-1953, 1958-1959, 1964-1965, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 997, Reel 14U)
    Ballistic Research Laboratory
  - United States Army, 1943, 1946-1948 January (Box 25, Folder 998, Reel 14U)
  - United States Army, 1948 February-March (Box 25, Folder 999, Reel 14U)
  - United States Army, 1948 April-1951, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 1000, Reel 14U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1946-1948 (Box 25, Folder 1001, Reel 14U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1949-1950 (Box 25, Folder 1002, Reel 14U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1951-1953 (Box 25, Folder 1003, Reel 14U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1954-1956 (Box 25, Folder 1004, Reel 14U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1005, Reel 15U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 1006, Reel 15U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 1007, Reel 15U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 1008, Reel 15U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1009, Reel 15U)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1970-1973, undated (Box 26, Folder 1010, Reel 15U)
  - United States House of Representatives, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 1011, Reel 15U)
  - United States Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1960-1961, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1012, Reel 15U)
  - United States Navy, 1945-1946, 1948, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 1013, Reel 15U)
  - Universität Tübingen, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 1014, Reel 15U)
    Institüt fur Theoretische Physik
  - Université de Liege, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 1015, Reel 15U)
  - Université de Nice, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 1016, Reel 15U)
  - Université de Paris, 1963, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1017, Reel 15U)
  - Universiteit van Amsterdam, 1952, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 1018, Reel 15U)
  - Universitetets Institut for Teoretisk Fysik, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 1019, Reel 15U)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1020, Reel 15U)
  - University Centers for Rational Alternatives, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1021, Reel 15U)
  - University of Arizona, 1967, undated (Box 26, Folder 1022, Reel 15U)
  - University of Calcutta, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1023, Reel 15U)
  - University of California at Berkeley, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1024, Reel 15U)
  - University of California at Davis, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1025, Reel 15U)
  - University of California at Los Angeles, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 1026, Reel 15U)
  - University of California at San Diego, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 1027, Reel 15U)
  - University of California at Santa Barbara, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1028, Reel 15U)
  - University of Cambridge, undated (Box 26, Folder 1029, Reel 15U)
  - University of Canterbury (New Zealand), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1030, Reel 15U)
  - University of Chicago, 1946, 1960-1961, 1964, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1031, Reel 15U)
  - University of Colorado, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1032, Reel 15U)
  - University of Connecticut, 1963, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1033, Reel 15U)
  - University of Illinois, 1938, 1944, 1956, 1968, undated (Box 26, Folder 1034, Reel 15U)
  - University of Iowa, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1035, Reel 15U)
  - University of Kansas, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 1036, Reel 15U)
  - University of Kentucky, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1037, Reel 15U)
  - University of Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 1038, Reel 15U)
  - University of Miami, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1039, Reel 15U)
  - University of Minnesota, 1946, 1956, 1958, 1960, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1040, Reel 15U)
  - University of Notre Dame, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 1041, Reel 15U)
  - University of Oregon, 1963, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1042, Reel 15U)
  - University of Otago, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1043, Reel 15U)
  - University of Rochester, 1958, 1960, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1044, Reel 15U)
  - University of Roorkee, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1045, Reel 15U)
  - University of Saugar, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 1046, Reel 15U)
  - University of Southern California, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 1047, Reel 15U)
  - University of Texas, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 1048, Reel 15U)
  - University of Tokyo, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1049, Reel 15U)
  - University of Toronto, 1965, undated (Box 26, Folder 1050, Reel 15U)
  - University of Virginia, 1955, 1957, 1965, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1051, Reel 15U)
  - University of Virginia, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 1052, Reel 15U)
    Rouss Physical Laboratory
  - University of Wichita, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 1053, Reel 15U)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1934, 1938, 1939, 1941, 1942, 1945-1946, 1948, 1954, 1966, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1054, Reel 15U)
  - University of Witswatersrand, Johannesburg, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1055, Reel 15U)
  - University of Wyoming, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1056, Reel 15U)
  - Urey, Harold C., 1959, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1057, Reel 15U)
  - Vallarta, M. S., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 1058, Reel 15U)
  - Van Allen, James A., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1059, Reel 15U)
  - Van Atta, Chet M., 1950, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 1060, Reel 15U)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 1061, Reel 15U)
  - Van Vleck, John H., 1938, 1951, 1954-1955, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 1062, Reel 15U)
  - Van Vleck, John H., 1958-1961, 1965-1971, undated (Box 26, Folder 1063, Reel 15U)
  - Vasile, Fochianu, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1064, Reel 15U)
  - Villi, Claudio, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1065, Reel 15U)
  - Vinti, John P., 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 1066, Reel 15U)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1067, Reel 15U)
  - Vogt, Erich W., 1962, undated (Box 26, Folder 1068, Reel 15U)
  - Von Behren, Patrick L., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1069, Reel 15U)
  - Von Neumann, John, 1948-1949, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 1070, Reel 15U)
  - W. A. Benjamin, Inc., 1962, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1071, Reel 15U)
  - W. B. Saunders Company, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1072, Reel 15U)
  - W. H. Freeman and Company, Publishers, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1073, Reel 15U)
  - Wadey, Geoff, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 1074, Reel 15U)
  - Walker, D., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 1075, Reel 15U)
  - Walker, W. D., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1076, Reel 15U)
  - Waller, Ivar, 1952, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 1077, Reel 15U)
  - Wannier, G., 1944 (Box 27, Folder 1078, Reel 15U)
  - Ward Howell Associates, 1953, 1955, 1957-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 1079, Reel 15U)
  - Wardman Park Hotel, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 1080, Reel 15U)
  - Washington Academy of Sciences, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1081, Reel 15U)
  - Washington Square College, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 1082, Reel 15U)
  - Washington University, 1957, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1083, Reel 15U)
  - Watanabe, Michael Satosi, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1084, Reel 15U)
  - Watson, Thomas J., 1953 (Box 27, Folder 1085, Reel 15U)
  - Watson, William H., 1946-1959, 1961, 1964, 1970, undated (Box 27, Folder 1086-1087, Reel 15U)
  - Watson Scientific Computing Laboratory, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 1088, Reel 15U)
  - Wayne State University, 1961, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1089, Reel 15U)
  - Weckering, Ralph, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1090, Reel 15U)
  - Weinburg, Alvin M., 1951-1953, 1958, 1960, 1964, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 1091, Reel 15U)
  - Weisskopf, Victor F., 1940-1941, 1951-1953, 1955, 1959, 1962, undated (Box 27, Folder 1092, Reel 15U)
  - Weissman, Barry, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1093, Reel 15U)
  - Wells, D. A., 1953 (Box 27, Folder 1094, Reel 15U)
  - Weneser, Joseph, 1956, 1958, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 1095, Reel 15U)
  - Wentzel, George, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 1096, Reel 15U)
  - Western Reserve University, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 1097, Reel 15U)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 1098, Reel 15U)
  - Wheeler, John Archibald, 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 1099, Reel 15U)
  - Wheeler, John Archibald, 1936-1938, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 1100, Reel 15U)
  - Wheeler, John Archibald, 1948-1950, 1952, 1954-1957, 1959-1965, 1968-1969, 1971-1972, undated (Box 27, Folder 1101, Reel 15U)
  - White, John A., undated (Box 27, Folder 1102, Reel 16U)
  - White, Milton G., 1956, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 1103, Reel 16U)
  - White House (Washington, D.C.), 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1104, Reel 16U)
  - Whitemore, Laurens E., 1968 (Box 27, Folder 1105, Reel 16U)
  - Who's Who in American Education, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 1106, Reel 16U)
  - Wick, Gian Carlo, 1947, 1964, undated (Box 27, Folder 1107, Reel 16U)
  - Wightman, A. S., 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1108, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1933-1934, 1938-1939, 1944, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 1109, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1948-1952 (Box 27, Folder 1110, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1111, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1112, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 1113, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1114, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1964-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1115, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1116, Reel 16U)
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1970-1973, undated (Box 28, Folder 1117, Reel 16U)
  - Wild, John F., 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1118, Reel 16U)
  - Wildermuth, Karl, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 1119, Reel 16U)
  - Wilets, Lawrence, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 1120, Reel 16U)
  - Wiley, C. A., 1950 (Box 28, Folder 1121, Reel 16U)
  - Wilkinson, Denys H., 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1122, Reel 16U)
  - Willard Hotel, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1123, Reel 16U)
  - William H. Clark Associates, Inc., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1124, Reel 16U)
  - Williams, John H., 1951, 1956, 1958, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1125, Reel 16U)
  - Williams, W. S. C., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 1126, Reel 16U)
  - Wills, L. A., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 1127, Reel 16U)
  - Wilson, Edwin Bright, 1953, 1955-1956, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1128, Reel 16U)
  - Wilson, John W., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 1129, Reel 16U)
  - Wilson, Richard, 1954, 1957-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1130, Reel 16U)
  - Wilson, Richard, 1964, 1968, undated (Box 28, Folder 1131, Reel 16U)
  - Wilson, Robert R., 1953, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 1132, Reel 16U)
  - Winslow, Allan M., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 1133, Reel 16U)
  - Winther, Aage, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 1134, Reel 16U)
  - Wisdom Hall of Fame, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 1135, Reel 16U)
  - Wolfenstein, Lincoln, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 1136, Reel 16U)
  - Wa Wong, Chun, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 1137, Reel 16U)
  - Wood, R. W., 1932 (Box 28, Folder 1138, Reel 16U)
  - World Who's Who, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 1139, Reel 16U)
  - Worthington, Hood, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 1140, Reel 16U)
  - Wright, S. Courtnay, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 1141, Reel 16U)
  - Wright, William E., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1142, Reel 16U)
  - Wright, William R., 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1143, Reel 16U)
  - Wu, C. S., 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1144, Reel 16U)
  - Wu, Ta-You, 1945, 1954-1955, 1966-1968, undated (Box 28, Folder 1145, Reel 16U)
  - Wyly, David, Jr., 1956, 1965, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1146, Reel 16U)
  - Yale Scientific Magazine, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1147, Reel 16U)
  - Yale University
    - General, 1946-1959 (Box 28, Folder 1148, Reel 16U)
    - General, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1149, Reel 16U)
    - General, 1964-1968, 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 1150, Reel 16U)
    - Department of Physics, 1954, 1959, 1961-1965, 1967, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1151, Reel 16U)
    - Graduate School, 1946-1947, 1950-1951, 1956-1958, 1961, 1963-1968, undated (Box 28, Folder 1152, Reel 16U)
    - Office of the President, 1946, 1948, 1954-1955, 1957, 1959-1960, 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1153, Reel 16U)
    - Office of the Provost, 1946, 1950, 1953-1956, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 1154, Reel 16U)
    - Office of the Provost, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1155, Reel 16U)
    - Office of the Provost, 1963-1964, 1966-1967, undated (Box 29, Folder 1156, Reel 16U)
    - Office of the Secretary, 1947, 1951-1955 (Box 29, Folder 1157, Reel 16U)
    - Office of the Secretary, 1956-1968, undated (Box 29, Folder 1158, Reel 17U)
    - Sloane Physics Laboratory, 1946-1947, 1949, 1953, 1956-1957, 1962-1963, undated (Box 29, Folder 1159, Reel 17U)
  - Yang, C. N. (Frank), 1957, 1963-1965, 1968-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 1160, Reel 17U)
  - Yeh, William Wen, 1965-1968 (Box 29, Folder 1161, Reel 17U)
  - Yennie, Donald R., 1956, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1162, Reel 17U)
  - Yeshiva University, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 1163, Reel 17U)
  - Ynterma, Jan L., 1952, 1954, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1164, Reel 17U)
  - Yock, Philip C. M., 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1165, Reel 17U)
  - Yoder, N. R., 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1166, Reel 17U)
  - Yost, Francis L., 1954, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1167, Reel 17U)
  - Yovits, Marshall C., 1951, 1954-1955, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1168, Reel 17U)
  - Ypsilantis, T. J., 1956 (Box 29, Folder 1169, Reel 17U)
  - Yukawa, Hideki, 1948-1949, 1953, 1956, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 1170, Reel 17U)
  - Zacharias, J. R., 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1171, Reel 17U)
  - Zahn, Charles T., 1955 (Box 29, Folder 1172, Reel 17U)
  - Zamick, L., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1173, Reel 17U)
  - Zernick, Wolfgang (Bill), 1962, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1174, Reel 17U)
  - Zickendraht, Werner, 1958-1964 (Box 29, Folder 1175, Reel 17U)
  - Zickendraht, Werner, 1967-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 1176, Reel 17U)
  - Zilsel, Paul, 1951-1956, 1963, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1177, Reel 17U)
  - Zinn, W., 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1178, Reel 17U)
  - Zondek, Bernd, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 1179, Reel 17U)
  - Zucker, Alexander, 1952-1958 (Box 29, Folder 1180, Reel 17U)
  - Zucker, Alexander, 1959-1961, 1963-1966, 1970, undated (Box 29, Folder 1181, Reel 17U)
  - Unidentified, 1934-1936, 1941, 1946, 1951, 1959, 1963-1965, 1967-1968, 1971, undated (Box 29, Folder 1182, Reel 17U)
- Diaries and Notebooks, 1935-1973; Series II; 1.5' (3 boxes)
  This series contains diaries and notebooks arranged by type of material.
  Materials in Series II, Diaries and Notebooks have been microfilmed. Patrons must use FILM HM 211 instead of the originals.
  - Diaries
    - 1941 (Box 30, Folder 1183, Reel 18U)
    - 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1183, Reel 18U)
    - 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1183, Reel 18U)
  - Course-related notebooks
    - Relativity lectures, 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 1184, Reel 18U)
    - Log of the seminar in theoretical physics, 1937-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1185, Reel 18U)
    - Applications of Group Theory to Quantum Mechanics course, 1950, [1950] (Box 30, Folder 1186, Reel 18U)
    - Colloquium at SUNY/Buffalo, 1969 October 30 (Box 30, Folder 1188, Reel 18U)
  - Conference and meeting notes
    - Visitors, 1939-1959 (Box 30, Folder 1189, Reel 18U)
    - 1946 September 15 - 1951 July 28 (Box 30, Folder 1190, Reel 18U)
    - 1954 January 25 - 1954 July 20, 1955 January 24 - 1955 September 29 (Box 30, Folder 1191, Reel 18U)
    - 1955 December 13 - 1957 February 28, 1957 March 13 - 1960 February 15, 1958 May 28 (Box 30, Folder 1192, Reel 18U)
    - 1959 March 16 - 1960 May 12 (Box 31, Folder 1193, Reel 18U)
    - 1960 February 1 - 1961 June 20, 1960 August 25 - 1962 February 13, 1961 September 1 - 1962 March 1 (Box 31, Folder 1194, Reel 18U)
    - 1962 January 24 - 1963 January 10, 1962 September 3 - 1966 April 12, 1963 October - 1964 July (Box 31, Folder 1195, Reel 19U)
    - 1964 August 5 - 1965 March 2, 1965 March 9 - 1966 October 26 (Box 31, Folder 1196, Reel 19U)
    - 1966 November 7 - 1968 September 3, 1968 August 29 - 1969 June 20 (Box 31, Folder 1197, Reel 19U)
    - 1969 August 26 - 1972 April 21 (Box 31, Folder 1198, Reel 19U)
  - Calculations and notes
    - Circa 1935, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 1199, Reel 19U)
    - 1943-1944, undated (Box 31, Folder 1200, Reel 19U)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 1201, Reel 19U)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 32, Folder 1202, Reel 20U)
    - undated (Box 32, Folder 1203, Reel 20U)
    - Nuclear calculations, undated (Box 32, Folder 1204, Reel 20U)
    - Field theories, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 1205, Reel 20U)
    - References - nuclear physics, [1935-1938?] (Box 32, Folder 1206, Reel 20U)
  - Logs
    - Loan of books and reprints, 1945-1973 (Box 32, Folder 1207, Reel 20U)
    - Record of visitors, 1948-1963 (Box 32, Folder 1208, Reel 20U)
- Additional Material, Circa 1929-1980; Series III; 32.5' (33 boxes)
  Series III, Additional Material, is unprocessed and unfilmed. Files are arranged by type of material. With the exception of the Notes, which are chronologically arranged, none of the material is arranged at the item level.
  - Writings
    - Reprints, Circa 1929-1969 (Box 33)
    - Manuscripts and typescripts of articles, Circa 1954-1973 (Box 34)
    - Manuscripts and typescripts of articles, Circa 1954-1973 (Box 35)
    - Manuscripts and typescripts of articles, Circa 1954-1973 (Box 36)
    - Manuscripts and typescripts of articles, Circa 1954-1973 (Box 37)
    - Manuscripts and typescripts of articles, Circa 1954-1973 (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts and typescripts of articles, Circa 1957-1973 (Box 39)
    - Reports of referee for the Physical Review, Circa 1957-1973 (Box 39)
    - Preprint/reprint mailing lists, Circa1957-1973 (Box 39)
  - Data files
    - Memos - Code "A" Series, Circa 1955-1968 (Box 40)
    - Memos - Code "A" Series, Circa 1955-1968 (Box 41)
    - Memos - Code "A" Series, Circa 1955-1968 (Box 42)
    - Memos - Code "B" Series, Circa 1959-1968 (Box 43)
    - Memos - I-XIII, Circa 1968-1974 (Box 44)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 45)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 46)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 47)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 48)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 49)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 50)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 51)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 52)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 53)